pakistaniscandals.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Scandals

Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Pakistaniscandals.com and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

Consumer Information  
During the process of delivering an ad to you, Pakistanicandals.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Pakistaniscandals.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected byPakistaniscandals.com is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers.

Third Party Advertising  
We use Adsense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser
